Catherine Viviano Gallery Records
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Files, 1945-1986, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-3; 3.5 linear feet)
  - Rollo, Joseph (Box 3)
    - List of Drawings and Invoice, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Artwork, undated, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 24-26)
    - Negative of Artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rosenthal, Bernard (Box 3)
    - Biographical Material, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1960, (9 folders) (Box 3, Folder 29-37)
    - Sales and Expenses, 1954-1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Press Releases, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Clippings, 1954-1960 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Guests Lists, circa 1954-1960 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - List of Artwork, circa 1952-1960 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Exhibition Catalogues and Invitation, 1953-1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Audubon Artists 11th Annual Prize for Sculpture, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Items, 1953-1962 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Photographs of Exhibition Installations (1959, undated), undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Photographs of Artwork (1952-1960, undated), undated, (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 47-52)
  - Sage, Kay circa 1958-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Von Ripper, Charles Rudolph (biographical material), circa 1960 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Wakabayashi, Kazuo (Box 3)
    - Biographical Material, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Guests Lists, 1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Wakabayashi of Brazil, Paintings, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Photographs of Kazuo Wakabayashi, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Photographs and Slides of Artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 3)
    - Biographical Material, 1951, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Checklists, circa 1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Consignment Sale Slips from the Grand Street Settlement, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - "Das Selbstportrait: Max Beckmann über Sein Leben Und Werk" by Doris Schmidt, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Notes and Lists, 1950-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Exhibition Catalogues, 1959-1970 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1939-1985, Series 2:; (Boxes 3-6; 5.5 linear feet)
  This series contains the gallery's general correspondence with artists, their family members, dealers, collectors, prospective clients, art historians, curators, museum directors, and others; correspondence with museums, galleries, and art-related institutions in the United States; and correspondence with museums, galleries, and art-related institutions abroad.
  Included with the correspondence are loan forms, consignment agreements, invoices, shipping receipts, printed materials, annotated exhibition catalogues, and photographs of artwork.
  Correspondence is arranged into 3 subseries:
  2.1: General Correspondence, 1939-1985
  2.2: Correspondence with Museums, Galleries, and Art-Related Institutions, United States, 1950-1984
  2.3: Correspondence with Museums, Galleries, and Art-Related Institutions Abroad, 1951-1975
  - General Correspondence, 1939-1985, 2.1:
    This subseries contains Viviano's correspondence with artists and their family members, historians, clients, publishers, and individuals at museums, galleries, and non-profit arts organizations. Included are letters from Margaret Viviano, who worked closely with her sister Catherine in the gallery. There are files of Catherine Viviano's scattered correspondence, some of it personal. Materials include carbon copies, drafts, postcards, telegrams, and photographs of artwork. Also found are illustrated letters, holiday and greeting cards, many with original artwork.
    Letters include detailed information on the gallery's general operations: acquisitions, sales, loans, shipping and delivery of artwork, insurance claims, and requests for biographical material on artists and permission to reproduce artwork. Letters also provide an overview of Viviano's efforts in promoting artists, developing relationships with clients and collectors, and organizing exhibitions. Among the artists frequently referred to in the correspondence are Afro and Mirko Basaldella, Max Beckmann, Renato Birolli, Robert Broderson, Leonardo Cremonini, Joseph Glasco, Luciano Minguzzi, Bernard Perlin, Faustus Pirandello, Bernard Rosenthal, and Kay Sage.
    The bulk of the correspondence with artists represented by the gallery is found in the artists' files. Some of the names in general correspondence can also be found in correspondence with galleries, museums, and art-related institutions in the United States and abroad.
    - Acheson, Helen - Adour, Tad, 1957-1966 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      Acheson, Helen
      Ackerman, Lloyd S.
      Adams, H. W.
      Adler, Thomas C.
      Adour, Tad
    - Ahlers, Jan - Albrecht, Phyllis, 1952-1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
      Ahlers, Jan
      Albrecht, Phyllis
    - Alcolay, Albert - Alsdorf, J. W., 1951-1964, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
      Alcolay, Albert
      Aldrich, Franny
      Aldrich, Larry
      Allen, Mrs. Francis Jebb
      Alsdorf, J. W. (Cory Corporation)
    - Alves, Lauro Mrs. - Appraiser Stores, 1950-1969, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
      Alves, Mrs. Lauro
      Ambassador Hotel
      Anderson, Donald James
      Anderson, Eleanor
      Andrus, John E.
      Angle, Everett E.
      Antoville, Maria
      Apollonio, Umbro (Archivio Storico D'Arte Contempranea della Biennale)
      Appraiser Stores, U.S. Customs, Treasury Department
    - Archenhold, Hans - Asher, Betty (Mrs. Leonard Asher), 1957-1976 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      Archenhold, Hans
      Armitage, Harold
      Armstrong, Mrs. Harris
      Artino, Frank S. J.
      Aruffo, Roy N.
      Ascher, Celia (McCrory Corporation)
      Asher, Betty (Mrs. Leonard Asher)
    - Askew, Kirk and Pamela, 1966-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Askin, Simon, Mrs. - Austin, Miss, 1952-1970 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      Askin, Mrs. Simon
      Associazione Universale di S. Antonio
      Auden, W. H.
      Austin, Miss
    - Ault, Lee and Dorothy,1953-1960, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Bahne, Salcia - Baker, Sylvia (Mrs. Oliver Baker),1950-1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
      Bahne, Salcia
      Baier, George F.
      Bainbridge, Katherine (Mrs. John S. Bainbridge)
      Baker, Harry
      Baker, Hollis S.
      Baker, Louis
      Baker, Sylvia (Mrs. Oliver Baker)
    - Baker, Richard Brown,1953-1960, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Baldaccini, César - Bangs, Christopher, 1955-1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
      Baldacchini, César
      Baldocchi, Mrs. Archie
      Ball, Charles W.
      Bangs, Christopher
    - Barbieri, Giussepe - Bareiss, Walter, 1955-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
      Barbieri, Giuseppe
      Barclay, Josephine (Mrs. John Barclay, Jr.)
      Bareiss, Walter
    - Barker, Walter (Art Department, University of North Carolina), 1963-1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Barneby, Rupert - Beard, Richard P., 1950-1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
      Barneby, Rupert B.
      Barnett, James E.
      Barr, Margaret
      Barter, Christie (Contemporary Slides)
      Barton, Bruce (Time Magazine)
      Barzilay, R. (Cimaise Magazine)
      Bassett, Florence Knoll
      Bator, Paul M.
      Bauduin, Armand
      Bayer, Joella
      Beard, Richard P.
    - Becker, Friederich - Benesch, Edward M., 1951-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
      Becker, Friederich
      Becker, Marion R.
      Becker, Rolf (Neue Galerie Im Künsterhaus)
      Beeson, Nora
      Bellocchio, Clelia
      Benesch, Edward M.
    - Beckmann, Peter and Maya,1967-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Benjamin, Helen (Mrs. Robert Benjamin) - Bergreen, Morris H., 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      Benjamin, Helen (Mrs. Robert Benjamin)
      Bergen, D. Thomas
      Bergen, Sidney and Corin
      Bergreen, Morris H.
    - Berman, Leonid - Bernstein, Janet (Mrs. Robert M. Bernstein), 1954-1976 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      Berman, Leonid
      Bernoudy, William Adair
      Berns, Mrs. Charles
      Bernstein, Janet (Mrs. Robert M. Bernstein)
    - Bilotti, Carlo 1972-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Bird, Genie - Blinken, Donald M., 1950-1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
      Bird, Genie
      Bishop, Elizabeth
      Bissett, Mrs.
      Blanton, Rosetta
      Blinken, Donald M.
    - Boer, Charles - Bonomi, Maria,1958-1979 (Box 3, Folder 87)
      Boer, Charles
      Bograd, Jacqueline
      Boigon, Helen W.
      Bonino, Giovanna
      Bonner, Bertram
      Bonomi, Maria
    - Boothroyd, R. H. - Boynton, George H., 1949-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
      Boothroyd, R. H.
      Bowen, Louis W.
      Bowery Savings Bank
      Bowlin, Josephine B.
      Bowness, Alan B.
      Boynton, George H.
    - Bradford, Susan - Brink-Rossato, Guido, 1950-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
      Bradford, Susan (Harry N. Abrams, Inc.)
      Bragaline, Edward A.
      Brammer, Caroline
      Bratby, John
      Bridges, Bernice (Young Adult Council of the National Social Welfare Assembly)
      Brigham, Mrs. Henry R.
      Brink-Rossato, Guido
    - Bright, David and Dolly,1958-1972 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Broderson, Betty - Brown, Peter A. G.,1950-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
      Broderson, Betty
      Brogan, Reverend Edward P.
      Broglio, Father
      Brown, Mrs. Eugene
      Brown, Mrs. Lowell H.
      Brown, Margaret E.
      Brown, Peter A. G.
    - Brown, Francis James, 1960-circa 1977 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Bruni, Claudio - Bunshaft, Gordon, 1955-1973, undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
      Bruni, Claudio
      Buchheim, L. G. (Buchheim Verlag)
      Buckley, Charles
      Bulley, Hugh
      Bunin, Max
      Bunnell, Mrs.
      Bunshaft, Gordon (Skidmore, Owings and Merrill)
    - Burden, William, A. M. - Buxton, Amalia (Mrs. Jorge Buxton), 1950-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
      Burden,William, A. M.
      Burgess, William H.
      Burns, Walter
      Burri, Alberto
      Butler, Charles
      Butler, John
      Buxton, Amalia (Mrs. Jorge Buxton)
    - Cabot, Petra - Canaday, John,1956-1976 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      Cabot, Petra
      Cadburry-Brown, H. T.
      Cahn, Joshua Binion (Mr. and Mrs. Joshua Cahn)
      Callahan and Fries
      Callaway, Leon L. (Newsweek Magazine)
      Callery, Mary
      Canaday, John
    - Cantor, Joseph - Carré, Louis,1950-1964, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
      Cantor, Joseph
      Caplan, Arthur
      Capogrossi, Giuseppe
      Cardas, Margery
      Carey, Jane C.
      Carré, Louis
    - Carter, Clarence - Cavellini, Achille,1951-1971, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
      Carter, Clarence
      Carter, Marjorie Lieberman
      Carter, Victor
      Castle, Muriel (Mrs. Irving Castle)
      Catlin, Theron E.
      Catto, Henry E. Jr., (Ambassador, United States Delegation to the Organization of American States)
      Cavallaro (forename illegible)
      Cavellini, Achille
    - Centenary United Methodist Church - Cherniavsky, Sally, 1950-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
      Centenary United Methodist Church
      Cerf, Walter
      Chadwick, Mrs. E. Gerry
      Chaet, Bernard
      Chambers, Marian Glasco
      Chase, Bob
      Cheney, Ward
      Cherkezian, Nazaret (National Education Television)
      Cherniavsky, Sally (Modern Art Annual)
    - Ching, William - Coates, Robert M., 1953-1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
      Ching, William
      Chisholm, Hugh
      Christensen, James
      Citron, Casper (The Casper Citron Program)
      Clark, Charles D.
      Clark, Jack
      Clifford, Henry
      Clough, Prunella
      Clough, Robert W. (Portuguese Cultural Foundation)
      Clyde, Mary Lee
      Coates, Robert M. (The New Yorker Magazine)
    - Coble, F. Garland - Cohen, Maurice M., 1951-1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
      Coble, F. Garland
      Codman, Florence
      Coen, Fabio
      Cohen, Debbie (Mrs. Zvi Cohen)
      Cohen, Maurice M.
    - Cole, Dana Stuart - Colten, Siegfried, 1951-1966, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Cole, Dana Stuart
      Cole, Richard
      Colin, Ralph (Rosenman, Goldmark, Colin and Kaye)
      Collias, James and Tina
      Colten, Siegfried
    - Consul General of Italy - Corbett, Mario, 1956-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Consul General of Italy
      Coombe, James
      Copeland, Elizabeth
      Copelin, Jeanette
      Copley, William
      Corbett, Mario
    - Costinescu, Silvelin von Scanzoni,1971-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Cowan, Robert - Cox, Denton Sayer, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Cowan, Robert
      Cowdrey, Bartlett
      Cowles, Mrs. Gardner
      Cowles, John
      Cox, Denton Sayer
    - Craft, Douglas - Crane, Louise, 1952-1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Craft, Douglas
      Cramer, Belle
      Crane, Louise
    - Crippa, Roberto - Cumming, Burton, 1951-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Crippa, Roberto
      Crosby, Caresse
      Crowley, M. J.
      Cuddeback, Charles H. (Douglas L. Elliman and Co.)
      Cullinan, Nina
      Cumming, Burton
    - Dahill, Elizabeth - D'Assia, Enrico, 1952-1976, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Dahill, Elizabeth
      Dailey, Lois (F. LeB. B. Dailey)
      D'Almeida, George
      D'Amelio, Joseph A.
      D'Angelo, Dino
      D'Artega, Vita Viviano
      D'Arquian, Maurice
      D'Assia, Enrico
    - Damaso, Jose - Daniels, David, 1957-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Damaso, Jose
      Damelin, Nancy (Mrs. Michael Damelin)
      Daniel, Harry M.
      Daniels, David
    - Darrow, Alex - Dayton, Bruce,1959-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Darrow, Alex
      Davis, Gene
      Davis, Hannah Seeger
      Davis, Richard
      Davis, Virginia Goodwyn
      Dayton, Bruce
    - Deacon, Richard - De Guigné, Charles,1957-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Deacon, Richard
      De Angelis, Erika
      De Cerralbo, El Marquis
      De Danby Ellen, O. S.
      De Guigné, Charles
    - DeHovitz, Bernard - Devernay, Joseph, 1956-1976, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
      DeHovitz, Bernard
      DeLamar, Alice
      De Menil, Dominque
      Demby, William
      Deuble, George, Jr.
      Devernay, Joseph
      Dexter, Richard
    - Di Valentin, Mrs. Louis - Dorazio, Piero and Virginia, 1956-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Di Valentin, Louis, Mrs. (Town of Greenburg UN Committee)
      Diebold, John
      Dietz, Leslie (Metropolitan Broadcasting)
      Dillinghouse, Louise
      Dine, Jim
      Dorazio, Piero and Virginia
    - Dratz, Edward F. - Dreyfus, Ernest and Ann, 1954-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Dratz, Edward F.
      Drew, Frances L. (Mrs. John Drew)
      Dreyfus, Ernest and Ann
    - Drouin, René - Duchamp, Marcel,1947-1960, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Drouin, René
      Du Baron, Edouard
      Dubuffet, Jean
      Dubbs, Jane
      Duchamp, Marcel
    - Dudensing, Valentine - Dwork, Melvin, 1961-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Dudensing, Valentine
      Dueñas, Roberto M.
      Dunbar, Jack and June
      Dutrow, Harold M.
      Dwork, Melvin
    - Eatou, Isabel Patterson - Ely, Geist C., 1954-1973, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Eatou, Isabel Patterson
      Ebb, Fred
      Edinburg, Joseph M.
      Edlich, T. J., Jr.
      Edwards, Augustin E.
      Einhorn, Nathan (The Library of Congress, Exchange and Gift Division)
      Eisendrath, William (City Art Museum of St. Louis)
      Ely, Geist, C.
    - Emmerich, André - Evans, Rex, 1957-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Emmerich, André
      Engel, A. Ferdinand (America-Italy Society)
      Entenza, John D.
      Erlanger, Michael
      Ernst, Dallas
      Escaruela, Andres
      Evans, Oliver
      Evans, Rex
    - Facchetti, Paul - Feiner, Wilhelmina Fox, 1960-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Facchetti, Paul
      Faison, S. Lane, Jr.
      Falk, Lawrence and Lucille
      Feiner, Wilhelmina Fox
    - Feltenstein, Harry and Lucille - Ferrareno-Wing, Elaine, 1952-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Feltenstein, Harry and Lucille
      Fenton, Edward
      Ferrareno-Wing, Elaine
    - Ferwerda, Floris and Nancy - Feyling Fred, A., 1958-1967, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Ferwerda, Floris and Nancy
      Feuche, Michael (J. Weingarten and Co.)
      Feyling, Fred A.
    - Field, Carolyn (Mrs. Joseph Field) - Fink, Francis S. (Mrs. Nathan Fink), 1955-1974, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Field, Carolyn (Mrs. Joseph Field)
      Field, Virginia C. (Mrs. Leonard Field)
      Field, Sampson R.
      Fink, Frances S. (Mrs. Nathan Fink)
    - Fischer, Friedheim - Fisher, Carl and Joan, 1959-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Fischer, Friedheim
      Fischer, Joseph O.
      Fisher, Carl and Joan
    - Fishman, Marvin L. - Fitzsimmins, James L., 1952-1976, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Fishman, Marvin L.
      Fitzgerald, Miro
      Fitzsimmons, James L.
    - Fleischman, Lawrence and Barbara - Florsheim, Richard A., 1949-1971, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Fleischman, Lawrence and Barbara
      Fleischman, Julius
      Fleming, Georgeann
      Florsheim, Richard A.
    - Fodera, Ben A. - Forman, Seymour, 1949-1971, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Fodera, Ben A.
      Ford, Charles Henri
      Ford, Geraldine C. (Mrs. Emory M. Ford)
      Forman, Seymour
    - Fortress, Karl - Franchina (forename omitted), 1958-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Fortress, Karl
      Fradkin, Samuel A.
      Franchetti, Giorgio
      Franchina (forename omitted)
    - Francis, Muriel Bultman - Frankenhauser, Neil, 1959-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Francis, Muriel Bultman
      Frank, Herbert
      Frankel, Egmont
      Frankenstein, Alfred V. (San Francisco Chronicle)
      Frankenhauser, Neil (Western Kentucky University, Department of Art
    - Franklin, Jack - Fuhri, William F., 1951-1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Franklin, Jack
      Franzen, Ulrich
      Freehling, Stanley M.
      Fuchs, Ernst
      Fuhri, William F.
    - Gabo, Miriam - Gallo, Avv. P. Alessandro, 1962-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Gabo, Miriam
      Gallo, Avv. P. Alessandro
    - Gansk, Sandra - Garvey, James M., 1959-1975, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Gansk, Sandra
      Ganz, Victor
      Garfield, Gustave B.
      Garvey, James M.
    - Gaylord, Barbara - Geary, John W., 1960-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
      Gaylord, Barbara
      Gaylord, Bradley
      Geary, John W.
    - Geiser, Elizabeth - Gersh, Philip, 1949-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
      Geiser, Elisabeth A. (R. R. Bowker Company)
      Genauer, Emily
      George, Thomas
      Gerhard, Aurelia
      Gersh, Philip
    - Gerson, Otto M. - Giacometti, Alberto, circa 1949-1961, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Gerson, Otto M. (Fine Arts Associates)
      Gettle, Stanley
      Ghiringhelli, Gino
      Giacometti, Alberto
    - Gibian, William - Gittlin, Richard, 1951-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
      Gibian, Willliam
      Gilchrist, Thomas B., Jr.
      Gill, Sister Mary Cyrille
      Gilvarry, James
      Ginsberg, Sidney and Ella
      Gittlin, Richard
    - Glasco, Gordon - Goldschmidt, Eve Benesch, 1961-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Glasco, Gordon
      Glasco, Marion
      Glasco, Pauline
      Glowacki, Stanley
      Goff, Lloyd Lozes
      Goldschmidt, Eve Benesch
    - Goodhue, Walter, 1952-1963, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Goodwin, Henry Sage - Goodyear, A. Conger, 1950-1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Goodwin, Henry Sage
      Goodwin, James Patrick
      Goodyear, A. Conger
    - Göpel, Erhard and Barbara, 1957-1977, undated, (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 38-41)
    - Gordewich, Igor - Goyen, William, 1950-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
      Gordewich, Igor
      Gordon, Ann
      Gordon, John
      Gordon, Martin
      Gorman, Sheridan P.
      Governaton, Arnoldo
      Goyen, William
    - Graham, Donald - Graves, Morris, 1954-1969 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      Graham, Donald
      Grakoest, Albert
      Granby, Julia (Mrs. Benjamin S.)
      Grand, Evalyne (Mrs. Julia H.)
      Grant, Jane (Mrs. R. D. Grant)
      Grass, Rubin
      Graves, Morris
    - Grazioni, Mario - Mrs. Milton Green, 1955-1977 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      Grazioni, Mario
      Greco, Emilio
      Green, Judith and William
      Green, Mrs. Milton
    - Greene, Anne (Mrs. J. B. Greene), 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Greenfield, Mrs. Albert - Griswold, W.E.S., 1955-1975, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
      Greenfield, Mrs. Albert
      Greenman, Paula
      Greenstein, Alvin
      Greenwich Savings Bank
      Gregory, Eric
      Gregory, William
      Griswold, W.E.S. (General Mills)
    - Gronland, Mary - Guerrero, José and Roxane, 1960-1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
      Gronland, Mary
      Grosman, Eugene M.
      Gross, Stanley J.
      Gruskin, Mrs. Alan D.
      Gudwin, Mrs. Robert (National Council of Women of the United States, Inc.)
      Guerrero, José and Roxane
    - Guggenheim, Charles - Guttoso, Renato, 1949-1969 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Guggenheim, Charles (Guggenheim Productions)
      Guillaume, Harry G. (University of Northern Iowa Department of Art)
      Gunn, Oskar Berry
      Guttoso, Renato
    - Haftman,Werner - Hall, Thomas, 1955-1966 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      Haftman, Werner
      Haid, David N.
      Hajdu, Etienne
      Hall, Thomas
    - Hamburger, Viktor - Mrs. McFadden Harrison, 1950-1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
      Hamburger, Viktor
      Hamilton, George Heard
      Harlan, Calvin
      Harper, Jane (Georges de Braux, Inc. Paintings)
      Harris, Allyn
      Harris, Arthur
      Harrison, Mrs. McFadden
    - Harvey, Robert - Haverstick, Ida S., 1955-1967 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Harvey, Robert
      Hatterer, Lawrence
      Haverstick, Ida S.
    - Helm, Michael - Herold, W. Alvin, 1952-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
      Helm, Michael
      Henderson, Harriet (Mrs. Wellington Harrison)
      Henderson, Mrs. Malcolm
      Hendrie, Betty
      Hennessey, Timothy
      Herbert, Don
      Herbert, Robert L. (Yale University, Department of the History of Art)
      Herold, W. Alvin
    - Heron, Patrick - Higgins, Georges, 1950-1973, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
      Heron, Patrick
      Herstein, Marianne Deson (Galleria Roma)
      Hess, John L. (New York Times)
      Heyer, George S.
      Higgins, Georges
    - Hilborn, Vivian W. - Himelstein, Miriam N., 1956-1967, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
      Hilborn, Vivian W.
      Hill, Timothy Osborne
      Hilton, Roger
      Himelstein, Miriam N. (Fleet Press Corporation)
    - Hirshhorn, Joseph - Hodes, Barnet 1950-1970 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      Hirshhorn, Joseph
      Hochman, John (Praeger Publishers, Inc.)
      Hodes, Barnet
    - Hodges, Ellie (Mrs. Loren Clifton Hodges) - Honigberg, Joel, 1955-1976 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      Hodges, Ellie (Mrs. Loren Clifton Hodges)
      Hogan, William Anthony
      Holman, Cranston W.
      Honigberg, Joel
    - Hook, Howard, J. - Hope, Michael, 1954-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
      Hook, Howard J.
      Hooker, Grace and Roger
      Hope, Michael
    - Hoskins, Beatrice (Mrs. Arthur Hoskins) - Hudson, Darrill, 1964-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
      Hoskins, Beatrice T. (Mrs. Arthur Hoskins)
      Howard, Charles
      Hudson, Darrill
    - Hulett, E. C. - Hunsicker, Robert C., 1954-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
      Hulett, E. C.
      Hume, Jaquelin H.
      Hunsicker, Robert C.
    - Hunt Roy A. - Hymes, Celia D., 1957-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
      Hunt, Roy A., Jr.
      Hunt, Torrence M.
      Hunt, William O.
      Hyatt, Derek
      Hymes, Celia D.
    - Igell, Herman - Istrati, Alexandre, 1955-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
      Igell, Herman
      Ingrao, Francesco
      Ireys, John Wells
      Istrati, Alexandre
    - Jacobs, Carl - Jaffe, Sam, 1952-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
      Jacobs, Carl
      Jacobs, Elizabeth R.
      Jacobs, Topsy (Mrs. Martin Jacobs)
      Jacoby, Alberta (Mrs. Irving Jacoby)
      Jaffe, Sam